<!DOCTYPE idea-plugin PUBLIC "Plugin/DTD" "http://plugins.intellij.net/plugin.dtd">
<idea-plugin url="http://idea-simsyn.tigris.org/">
    <name>Extended Syntax Highlighting for IDEA6</name>
    <description>
        Provides extended syntax highlighting based on user-definable configuration files. Use
        'Init SimpleSyntax' from Tools menu to install syntax highlighting. Clone files
        in your IDEA 'config/options/SimpleSyntax' folder to enable highlighting for other
        languages. Use 'Reload SimpleSyntax' form Tools menu to reload configuration changes.
        ///
        In contrast to the Simple Syntax Highlighting plugin, this one uses more advanced lexer
        definitions. Sorry for the lack of documentation.
        ///
        Credits: Includes the wonderful Groovy, JRuby and JParsec systems. Also included are
        a few files from the pythonid Python plugin.
    </description>
    <change-notes>
        [ V0.19 ] Added support for dynamic JFlex-based syntax definitions. Added Python example configuration
        [ V0.18 ] Switched to Groovy and JRuby lexer configuration using JParsec.
        [ V0.17 ] Fully fixed for IDEA 6.0. Now highlighting of files works properly again.
        [ V0.16 ] Fixed for IDEA 6.0. No more crashing IDEA 6.0 and later.
        [ V0.15 ] Fixed more minor issues in Ruby highlighting.
        [ V0.14 ] Fixed quirk in ColorSettingsPage when defining several rules for a syntax token.
        [ V0.13 ] Fixed duplicate file type issue. (Occurred when using 'Reload SimpleSyntax'.)
        [ V0.12 ] Speeded up example Ruby configuration by removing all 'ruby' and adding 'regex' tokens. Improved 'regex' performance.
        [ V0.11 ] Cleaned up resource/file access codebase. Moved configuration to 'config/options/SimpleSyntax' subfolder.
        [ V0.10 ] Fixed groovy rule implementation. Fixed DOC_COMMENT issue.
        [ V0.9 ] Improved Ruby example configuration. Fixed locked config file issue.
        [ V0.8 ] Implemented global registry collision work around when using more than one configuration.
        [ V0.7 ] Fixed minor (doc) issues after first (offical) plugin release. Fixed reloading of token colors/attributes.
        [ V0.6 ] Added 'groovy' syntax rule.
        [ V0.5 ] Added reload action.
        [ V0.4 ] Added init action.
        [ V0.3 ] Added 'ruby' syntax rule.
        [ V0.2 ] Implemented syntax configuration loading.
        [ V0.1 ] Initial release with hardcoded Ruby syntax.
    </change-notes>
    <version>0.19</version>
    <vendor email="simplesyntax@intensicode.net" url="http://www.intensicode.net">IntensiCode</vendor>
    <idea-version since-build="5000" until-build="6499"/>
    <application-components>
        <component>
            <implementation-class>net.intensicode.idea.SimpleSyntax</implementation-class>
        </component>
    </application-components>
    <actions>
        <action id="SimpleSyntaxInstall" class="net.intensicode.idea.ActionInstall"
                text="Init SimpleSyntax" description="Install the default SimpleSyntax configuration for Ruby">
            <add-to-group group-id="ToolsMenu" anchor="last"/>
        </action>
        <action id="SimpleSyntaxReload" class="net.intensicode.idea.ActionReload"
                text="Reload SimpleSyntax" description="Purge and reload the SimpleSyntax configurations">
            <add-to-group group-id="ToolsMenu" anchor="last"/>
        </action>
    </actions>
</idea-plugin>
